

MARCO GUNAWAN

Fullstack Developer

C

+6281947387912



mgunawan10@gmail.com



LinkedIn

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering Mercu Buana University 2018-2023

EXPERTISE

Technical Skills:

- 1.PHP, ReactJS, Laravel,Flutter, Codelgniter 4
- 2.RESTful APIs, SQL, OOP, Query Builder
- Git, Docker, Composer, Nginx, MySQL/PostgreSQL

ERP Development:

- 1.Logistics, finance, and quality control systems
- 2.Learning Management Systems
- 3. Quality Control tools

Database Management:

- 1.Raw SQL queries and optimization
- 2. Production Planning:
- 3. Material stock control
- 4. Production forecasting
- 5.Cost calculation and quotation preparation

Soft Skills:

- 1.Mentoring and team leadership
- 2. Strategic planning and process optimization
- 3.Cross-functional collaboration

PROFILE

Hello, I'm Marco Gunawan, a professional with expertise in accounting, production planning, and IT programming. I specialize in full-stack web development for ERP systems, using PHP, Codelgniter, Flutter, Laravel, and SQL. With strong analytical skills, I excel at bridging technology and business operations. Let's connect to explore how I can contribute to your team!

WORK EXPERIENCE

Abhati Group

2023 - Present

Fullstack Developer

- Work effectively both in a team and independently.
- Develop new applications, including mobile and web apps.
- Maintain existing applications by fixing bugs and adding useful features as needed.
- Continuously learn and implement new technologies to enhance application capabilities.
- Mentor new hires as a senior programmer.
- Quickly adapt to and understand ERP business workflows within six months

PT. Nijes Bayu Lestari

2021 - 2023

PPIC (Production Planning Inventory Control)

- Controlling Stock materials
- Create planning production for future forecast
- Calculate work cost, transport cost, packing cost for Quotation
- Emailing and Communicate with the supplier

PT. Nijes Bayu Lestari

2018-2021

Accounting Staff

- Make Monthly income report
- Make a monthly Cash flow report
- Reporting monthly tax invoice
- · Invoicing and mailing